rsm.nl 2019-03-06

# Privacy Statement - About RSM - Home - Rotterdam School of Management, Erasmus University

Rotterdam School of Management, Erasmus University (RSM) will treat the personal data of visitors to her website(s) with care. Personal data are processed and secured in accordance with the applicable law and the General Data Privacy Regulation (hereafter together referred to as the “ **Act** ”).

**Controller** \- RSM is the data controller in accordance with the Act. RSM will decide which personal data are processed, for which purpose, and in which way. RSM shall processes personal data in a careful manner and in accordance with the Act. 

**Processing personal data** – Personal data are all data that can provide information about an identifiable person. RSM collects personal data of visitors to her website(s), including but not limited to the IP address of visitors. General data about the visit to her website(s) (analytics) are also collected. 

**Purpose** – RSM uses personal data for one or more of the following purposes:

• Offering education and educational services;  
• Provision of information related to educational activities;   
• Invitations to visit the school and campus, seminars, Massive Open Online Courses (MOOCS), promotions, and other meetings held about education;   
• Maintaining relationships with RSM alumni;   
• Candidate selection for educational programs;   
• Personal meeting, including phone conversations and/or Skype (or similar) conversations with (potential) students of RSM;   
• Organizing RSM campus tours;   
• Access to Job Board. 

Personal data which you have provided to RSM, will be processed and used to contact you to meet the purposes set out above. In case you do not wish to receive information from RSM, you will able to opt out.

**Legal ground for processing** – Processing of personal data by RSM is necessary the meet the legitimate interests of RSM. For some specific purposes RSM will ask prior consent from the data subject.

**Security** \- RSM guaranteed that she has taken suitable technical and organizational measures to prevent the loss of personal data or unlawful processing of personal data. This includes, but it not limited to, encryption of personal data, and using only secure connections to move personal data.

**Term of storage of personal data** \- RSM will store your personal data as long as is necessary for processing purposes, and no longer.

**Register** \- RSM will keep a register of all processing activities that take place under her control.

**Your rights** – You have the right to review your personal data, and the right to request correction or removal of your personal data. If you wish to know which personal data RSM processes, you can submit a request in writing. RSM will respond to your request within four (4) weeks. Should your data be incomplete, incorrect or irrelevant, you can submit an additional request to amend or compete your data.

You can send written requests to: Bestuurlijke en Juridische Zaken: legal.advice@eur.nl and/or Privacy@eur.nl 

The Erasmus University Rotterdam has a data privacy officer: [Privacy@eur.nl](mailto:Privacy@eur.nl)
